WITH THE 53RD PICK IN THE 2026 NFL
DRAFT.
The AFC South Kings Indianapolis Colts
select
CJ ALLEN, LINEBACKER FROM GEORGIA.
Go Dogs.
They not only just got a linebacker to
put in their middle of their defense,
they got a leader that they can
establish in the middle of their
defense. You see CJ Allen there
>> very emotional celebrating.
>> Very good chance he could have heard his
name last night. He falls into the
second round into this range. And it's
the good fortune of the Indianapolis
Colts and Chris Ballard. This is someone
who established himself the second he
got on campus at Georgia. It's hard to
get on the field there. He didn't have
any issues. He's very quick to trigger.
trust his eyes, get around blocks, and
navigate his way towards the football.
He was a tackle machine for that Bulldog
defense. Here's the closing burst. That
pro day for him was very late in the
process, and I thought maybe he lost a
little ground because it took so long
for him to get out there. He ran really
fast, and you can see it in his tape.
Here's some of those zone instincts and
coverage. I think he's got a chance to
be he's got a chance to beat the best
off the ball linebacker in this entire
draft class, and that's saying
something. But that's the type of talent
that he possesses, Charles.
>> And much more of a pure off the ball old
style linebacker when we're talking
about Styles Reese. We're talking about
guys that do a few more things that way.
But Joel
Daniel mentioned, you know, this guy's a
tackling machine.
>> Yeah,
>> remember they just lost their tackling
machine and Zair Franklin who was
putting up 100 and a half every year.
This guy gets a chance to step right in
and be that person.
>> The people in Georgia would say he was
the heart and soul of that defense. And
you talked about how early he saw the
field for Kirby. Not easy to do. He made
a name for himself on the scout team.
>> CJ,
>> how you doing?
>> How you doing, man? This Chris Bower
with the Indianapolis Colts.
>> I'm doing great. I'm doing better now.
>> Good. Welcome to Indie, man. We're going
to take you right here.
>> Let's do it. Let's do it.
>> All right, man. No, we're excited. We're
excited.
CJ, let's go.
>> CJ,
>> high around the room.
>> Yeah, KO.
>> Yes, sir, baby. Yes, sir.
>> What's going on, man? It's Coach Ber,
your new linebacker. Coach, baby, you
fired up.
>> Oh, man. I'm fired up, dude. I know
that. I know that. We're excited to have
you, man. We'll talk to you soon, CJ.
Don't scream. Good for him. What we got
to do?
>> Good fans.
>> Good for us.
>> Great for us.
>> Great for us. Great for us. Yeah. Good
work, man. Better work.
>> Let's go, man. I'm so excited to be a
coach, man. Let's do it, man. You
getting a player. I'm ready to work,
man. Let's do it. LET'S WORK
>> WITH THE 78TH PICK IN THE 2026 NFL
DRAFT. LIVE FROM PITTSBURGH,
PENNSYLVANIA,
the Indianapolis Colts select AJ Huly DB
out of LSU.
>> They went shopping to fix the the middle
of their defense in the SEC. They've
already done it with the linebacker and
CJ Allen. Now they go get AJ Hally, who
reminded me framewise of Lannon Collins.
that thick kind of stout build as
someone who also will play in the middle
of the field at that size. And then
watch him plant and drive. He's really
good at reading the quarterback and
positioning himself to make plays on the
football. Here he is doing it down in
the red zone and doing it in in the SEC
at a very high level. Here's that
physical presence that he brings. Also
some leadership he's going to bring to
that defense. They've drafted two guys
in the Miller defense that are leaders
that are very productive in Allen and
now in Holly. AJ,
>> this is Chris Tyler with the Colts. You
excited? We're going to take you right
here. Congrats, man.
>> Let's do it. Let's Come get me,
>> AJ. Fire up.
>> How you doing?
>> You fired up?
>> Let's do it.
>> Let's go, baby.
>> Let's do it. I waited too long. Let's do
it.
>> Hell yeah. Congratulations, man. I'm
excited for you, man.
>> I love it. I love it.
WE GOT
>> like that one.
>> Thank you.
>> We have that in our
>> CJ. That's a great
>> I know.
>> He said, "Come get me now. I'm ready.
Congratulations.
>> Yes, it's good.
>> Hey man, you will that
>> we get the linebacker one of those D
line
>> and we get the safety one of those guys
in the third round.
>> Say that.
>> You said it.
>> We'll take it.
>> And I like he got big strong hands.
Catch the ball. Catch the ball.
>> Like the ball is like stuck in there.
>> He's a man.
>> He grown man.
>> Yes sir.